Guide to the Humanities Advisory Committee, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Humanities Advisory Committee, Yale University, records
1985-1991
RU 853
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
1
(1 box)
The records consist of minutes, reports, plans, and correspondence documenting the activities of the Humanities Advisory Committee at Yale. The records were maintained by Wayne A. Meeks.
Whitney Humanities Center
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 37 (YRG 37), Records of associations, institutes, centers, and organizations affiliated with Yale University.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the records is restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Arrangement
The records are arranged chronologically.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of minutes, reports, plans, and correspondence documenting the activities of the Humanities Advisory Committee at Yale. The records were maintained by Wayne A. Meeks.
Humanities -- Study and teaching; Whitney Humanities Center; Yale University -- Curricula
- Records of Wayne A. Meeks as a member of the Humanities Advisory Committee, Yale University, 1985-1991; Accession 2000-A-023
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2036
  - 1990-1991
    - Current business (Box 1)
    - Minutes (Box 1)
    - Correspondence (Box 1)
    - Dept. reviews (Box 1)
    - Appointment procedures (Box 1)
    - Tenure appointment committee (Box 1)
  - 1989-1990
    - Dept. reviews (Box 1)
    - Current (Box 1)
    - Minutes (Box 1)
    - Correspondence (Box 1)
    - Exp. Executive committee (Box 1)
    - Language report (Box 1)
    - Assorted reports (Box 1)
  - 1988-1989
    - Current business (Box 1)
    - Tenure appointment committee (Box 1)
    - Correspondence (Box 1)
    - Minutes (Box 1)
    - Senior appointment committee (Box 1)
  - 1987-1988
    - Islamic studies (Box 1)
    - Minutes and reports (Box 1)
    - Yale College committees (Box 1)
    - Af/Am Af review (Box 1)
  - 1986-1987 (Box 1)
  - 1985-1986 (Box 1)